现在，在我们开始编写一行代码之前，
Now before we can start writing a single line of code,
我们首先需要安装一个特殊的工具
we first need to install a special tool
称为代码编辑器。
called a code editor.
代码编辑器本质上是一种特殊的软件
And a code editor is essentially a special software that
允许我们编写 HTML 和 CSS 等编程代码
allows us to write programming code like HTML and CSS
以一种非常简单的方式。
in a very easy way.
而且由于这门课程可能是您第一次接触
And since this course is probably your first contact with
任何编码和这个视频我会指导你
any coding and this video I will guide you
通过安装世界上最好的代码编辑器。
through installing the very best code editor in the world.
然后我还将向您展示如何设置它
And I will then also show you how to set it up a little bit
带有一些特殊设置、颜色主题和扩展。
with some special settings, color themes and extensions.
以及我们将在本课程中使用的代码编辑器
And the code editor that we're going to use in this course
被称为 Microsoft 的 Visual Studio 代码。
is called visual studio code from Microsoft.
我刚才是否说过，在我看来，
And has I just said earlier, this is in my opinion,
在许多其他开发人员看来，
and in the opinion of many other developers,
世界上最好的 Web 开发代码编辑器。
the very best code editor for web development in the world.
所以实际上我现在认识的每个开发者
So actually every developer that I know right now
使用此代码编辑器。
uses this code editor.
因此，使用 vs 代码也不会出错。
And so you also can't go wrong by using vs code.
所以要下载它，
So to download it,
只需访问 code.visualstudio.com 或
just go to code.visualstudio.com or
为了让它更容易，你可以只用谷歌 vs 代码。
to make it even easier, you can just Google vs code.
这应该是第一个结果。
And it should be this very first result.
当然，vs code 是免费提供的
And of course, vs code is available for free
并适用于所有平台。
and for all platforms out there.
所以 Mac OS、Windows 和 Linux。
So Mac OS, windows, and Linux.
所以请立即下载
And so please just go ahead right now and download the
您自己的系统的安装程序。
installer for your own system.
然后在你的电脑上安装程序，
Then install the program on your computer,
就像任何其他程序一样。
just like any other program.
然后，一旦你完成了，
And then once you're done doing that,
回到这个视频，这样我们就可以设置
just come back to this video so that we can set up
你的编辑一点点。
your editor a little bit.
好的。
Okay.
所以我希望你设法安装了 Visual Studio 代码
So I hope that you managed to install visual studio code
或 vs 代码，我们也在您的计算机上调用它。
or vs code as we also call it on your computer.
一旦你打开代码编辑器，
And once you open up the code editor,
它应该看起来像这样。正如我之前所说，
it should look something like this. And as I said earlier,
我们现在将设置一个 vs 代码
we will now set up a vs code a little bit
让您更轻松地学习本课程。
to make it easier for you to follow this course.
我们将从安装扩展开始。
And we will start by installing an extension.
而且vs code的扩展基本上只是一小块
And an extension for vs code is basically just a small piece
我们可以下载的功能
of functionality that we can download and which makes the
编辑器好一点。
editor a little bit better.
所以我们基本上可以根据自己的需要自定义编辑器。
So we can basically customize the editor to our needs.
所以你可以把它想象成谷歌浏览器
So you can think of it a little bit like Google Chrome
扩展名，例如。
extensions, for example.
所以是同一个概念。
So it's the same concept.
我们现在要安装的那个
And the one that we're going to install for now
被称为更漂亮。因此，只需搜索更漂亮。
is called prettier. So just search for prettier.
然后这可能是这里的第一个结果
And then it's probably going to be this first result here
因为 prettier 是一个非常流行的扩展。
because prettier is an extremely popular extension.
您会看到它现在有超过 1200 万次下载。
You see it has over 12 million downloads right now.
所以请继续点击此处安装
And so just go ahead and click install here
然后启用它。
and then enable it.
然后你可能还必须重新加载
And probably you will then have to also reload
这与代码窗口。
this vs code window.
现在这个扩展的作用是自动格式化你的
Now what this extension does is to automatically format your
每当你保存它的代码。
code whenever you save it.
这将非常重要，因此您的代码
And this is going to be very important so that your code
总是看起来与代码完全相同
always looks exactly the same way as the code that
我正在输入视频，
I am typing in the video,
因为这样你会更容易找到任何
because that way it will be way easier for you to find any
错误或您在自己的代码中遇到的任何错误。
errors or any mistakes that you have in your own code.
因此，您将更容易找到并修复错误
So it will be easier for you to find and to fix mistakes
当您浏览视频时。
as you're going through the videos.
好的。而现在，
Okay. And for now,
这实际上将是唯一的扩展
this is actually going to be the only extension that
我们要安装。我们将安装更多
we're going to install. We will just install some more
稍后在下一节中。
a bit later in the next section.
所以现在让我们来到这个设置图标，
So now let's come down here to this settings icon,
然后从这里选择设置，以便我们现在可以调整
then choose settings from here so that we can now tweak a
几个设置。
couple of settings.
让我们从两个相关的设置开始
And let's actually start with two settings that are related
到我们刚刚安装的更漂亮的扩展。
to the prettier extension that we just installed.
所以就到这里来搜索栏吧。
So just come here to the search bar.
所以搜索设置名称其实是最简单的
So searching for the setting name is actually the easiest
找到它们的方法。
way of finding them.
因此，只需在此处键入默认格式化程序。
So just type here, default formatter.
所以在这里，我们实际上需要将它设置为更漂亮。
And so here, we actually need to set it to prettier.
所以我当然已经设置好了，
So I already have it set of course,
但你必须通过这个列表
but you will have to go through this list
并在这里找到更漂亮的地方。
and find prettier somewhere here.
所以它就在这里。
So it is right here.
所以，选择更漂亮的代码格式化程序，
So, choose prettier code formatter,
它必须是这件 esbnp.prettier-vs 外套。
and it needs to be this esbnp.prettier-vs coat.
好的。
Okay.
所以现在 vs code 知道它应该使用更漂亮的
And so now vs code knows that it should use that prettier
我们刚刚安装的扩展程序来格式化您的代码。
extension that we just installed to format your code.
现在，它应该什么时候真正格式化您的代码？
Now, when should it actually format your code?
好吧，我们需要为此设置另一个设置，
Well, we need to set another setting for that,
这是安全设置的格式。
which is the format on safe setting.
所以这是这里，这里
So it's this one here, and here
您需要选中此复选框，以便更漂亮
you need to check this checkbox so that prettier will
每次自动格式化您的文件
automatically format your file each time
你保存它。
that you save it.
好的。
Okay.
另一个非常重要的是自动安全设置。
Another one that is very important is the auto safe setting.
所以自动安全，我们需要将它设置为 onFocusChange。
So auto safe, we need to set it to onFocusChange.
这将自动将您的文件另存为
And what this will do is to automatically save your files as
您转到另一个选项卡或完全离开窗口时。
you go to another tab or as you leave the window completely.
所以这很重要，这样你就永远不会失去你的
And so this is very important so that you never lose your
编辑，这样您就不必手动保存文件
edits and so that you don't have to manually save your files
每时每刻。
all the time.
因此，再次将其设置为 onFocusChange。
So set this one to onFocusChange again.
还有一个我喜欢用的，
And another one that I like to use,
而且我不确定这是否实际上已经是默认设置
and I'm not sure if this is actually the default already
是将标签大小设置为两个。
is to set the tab size to two.
所以在这种情况下，这又是一次，
And so in this case, this is just again,
这样您的代码看起来与我的代码完全相同。
so that your code looks exactly the same way as my code.
所以标签大小基本上只是缩进
So the tab size is basically just the indentation of the
代码，稍后你就会知道这意味着什么，
code and you will know what that means a little bit later,
一旦我们开始编写 HTML，就可以了。
once we start writing HTML, okay.
这就是我们需要设置的四个设置。
And these are the four settings that we need to set.
所以我认为我们现在的设置很好。
So I think we're good now with the settings.
现在最后，让我们谈谈这些颜色。
And now finally, let's talk about these colors.
所以基本上我们可以用颜色主题自定义 vs 代码，
So basically we can customize vs code with a color theme,
然后将更改代码编辑器本身的颜色
which will then change the colors of the code editor itself
还有代码。
and also of the code.
所以它基本上会突出代码的不同部分
So it will basically highlight different parts of the code
用不同的颜色。
with different colors.
现在，这只是个人喜好。
Now, this is just a thing of personal preference.
所以你可以使用已经出现的主题
So you can just use the theme that already comes
默认情况下自动使用 vs 代码。
automatically by default with vs code.
但我选择安装一个我认为可以制作的特殊主题
But I choose to install a special theme that I believe makes
很容易阅读代码。
it very easy to read the code.
因此，您可以更轻松地学习本课程。
And so for you to follow this course in an easier way.
所以颜色主题基本上只是另一个扩展
So a color theme is basically just another extension
我们需要安装。
that we need to install.
而这个叫做One Monokai。
And this one is called One Monokai.
所以这是这里的第一个，正如你在这里看到的，
So this very first one here, and as you can see down here,
它会给我们的代码这些颜色，
it will give our code these kinds of colors,
而且 vs 代码编辑器本身也会
and also the vs code editor itself will
有这个你可以在这里看到的蓝色
have this blue color that you can see already here
在这个窗口中。
in this window.
所以如果你也想使用这个颜色主题来制作你的
So if you want to use this color theme as well to make your
编辑器和我的一模一样
editor look exactly the same as mine,
然后继续前进，再一次，
then just go ahead and once again,
下载此扩展，然后使用设置颜色主题
download this extension and then set the color theme using
这个选项在这里。
this option here.
你也可以尝试一些其他的主题，
And you can also experiment with some other themes,
当然，再次在这里，在设置图标中。
of course, down here, again, in the settings icon.
然后在颜色主题中，
And then here in color theme,
您可以选择这些轻主题之一或其中之一
you can choose one of these light themes or one of these
黑暗的主题。
dark themes.
所以 vs code 已经自带一堆主题了
So vs code already comes with a bunch of themes
基本都是预装的。
pre-installed basically.
所以你也可以尝试一下。
And so you can try them out as well.
或者，如果您有其他偏好，
Or if you have another preference,
您还可以安装您想要的任何其他主题。
you can also install any other theme that you would like.
最后，还有一件小事，
Finally, there's just one more small thing,
这是我可以主题的这些文件。
which is these file I can theme.
所以这个其实无所谓
So this doesn't really matter,
但我在这里设置了这个选项。所以塞提。
but I set mine to this option here. So Seti.
再说一次，
And so again,
如果你想让你的编辑器看起来和我的一样，
if you want your editor to look just like mine,
您也可以继续选择此选项。
you can also go ahead and choose this option.
好的，那么我们现在已经完成了 vs 代码的设置。
Okay, then that we are done setting up vs code for now.
所以现在你已经准备好写了
So now you're actually ready to write
你的第一行代码。
your very first line of code.
这正是我们要做的
And so that's exactly what we're going to do
在下一个视频中。
in the next video.
很快就在那里见。
See you there soon.